AMMAD ASLAM

UI/UX Designer

CONTACT

- **** +92 319 8147269
- m.ammad1999@yahoo.com
- House 629, Street 23/c, Mehmodabad no 5, Karachi

SKILLS

- User Experience Design
- User Interface Design
- User Flows
- Prototyping
- Wireframing

TOOLS

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop

PORTFOLIO

- in www.linkedin.com/in/ammadaslam12
- Bē www.behance.net/ammadaslam1

PROFILE

Accomplished UI/UX Designer wth more than 1 year of experience. Eager to make a positive impact by bringing in creativity and versatility with fresh, clean and minimalist approach to design and enchancing user experience. Seeking a position in the organization where the opportunity of continuous growth and career development, that motives me to the fullest.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer

Ossols Pvt Ltd | Dec 2022 - Present

- Develop user-centered designs by understanding user needs, behaviors, and motivations through research and analysis.
- Create wireframes, mockups, and prototypes to effectively communicate design ideas and interactions.
- Design visually appealing interfaces that adhere to brand guidelines while focusing on usability and accessibility principles.
- Stay updated with industry trends, best practices, and emerging technologies in UI/UX design to continuously improve skills and stay innovative.

UI/UX Designer

Golpik | Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

- Presented prototypes and concept designs using Adobe XD.
- Collaborate with other designers to maintain design consistency.
- Collaborated and communicated effectively with technical & non-technical individuals.

Graphic & UI/UX Designer

Technomites | 2021 - 2022

- Designing mockups using tools like Photoshop and Adobe XD.
- Understanding user requirements.
- Redesigning websites to enhance the user experience.
- Designing Banners, Social media posts and Logos.

EDUCATION

ACCP Prime (2017 - 2020)

Aptech Learning Shahrah-e-Faisal Centre

Intermediate in Pre Engineering (2016 - 2017)

PECHS Foundation College

Matriculation in Computer Science (2015 - 2016)

The Educators